yoga.com 2016-02-01

# Privacy Policy | YOGA.com

At yoga.com, We (Snapside Trading Limited and its affiliates) respect Your privacy and are committed to protecting Your personal information. Snapside has created this Privacy Policy to let You know what information We collect when You use yoga.com and make use of our service and Software (collectively, the "Service"), why We collect this information and how We use the collected information and for You to understand Your rights and obligations in relation to that information. By using the Service, You consent to the data practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change. It is Your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Software following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes. By accessing our website yoga.com or otherwise using our service, You consent to our information practices.

## Collection and Use of Information

We receive and store information, including personal information, about You and Your use of our Service, as further detailed below. This information is gathered in a number of ways, including when You enter it on our website yoga.com and from interactions with our Service. Personal information is information that can be used to uniquely identify or contact You. Non-personal information is information that does not permit direct association with You. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. You can choose not to provide personal information we may request of You, but, in general, most of the personal information We request is required in order to provide our service and the lack of such personal information will prevent Us from doing so.

## Information about You Received by Us

When You use yoga.com, You allow Snapside to access certain information from Your profile. Snapside may access and store some or all of the following information, as allowed by You, and Your preferences:

  * Your first and last name;
  * Your profile picture or its URL;
  * Your user ID number, which is linked to publicly available information such as name and profile photo;
  * the login e-mail You provided;
  * Your physical location and that of Your access devices;
  * Your gender;
  * date of your birthday.

When You interact with Us, we may ask You to supply us with personal information so that We can provide, enhance and personalize our Services and marketing efforts. For similar reasons, We may supplement the personal information You provide with publicly available information about You as well as information from other sources, as permitted by law. We use this personal information, for example, to process Your registration, and to communicate with You. We also may use Your e-mail address or other methods to send You newsletters, as well as messages about new yoga.com features, yoga.com special offers, promotional announcements, consumer surveys and other correspondence concerning the use of yoga.com. If You no longer want to receive certain communications from Us, You can simplyunsubscribe. Please note that You cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from Us.

We keep track of Your interactions with Us and collect information related to You and Your use of our service, including but not limited to: Your online activity, title selections, reviews, ratings, correspondence, Internet protocol addresses, device types, unique device data (such as device identifiers), operating systems, and related activity. We use this information for such purposes as determining Your general geographic location, providing localized content, enforcing our terms personalizing the Service to better reflect particular interests, determining Your Internet service provider, helping Us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise enhancing or administering our Service offering for You and other users. We also provide analysis of Our users in the aggregate or otherwise in anonymous form to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. 

While using the yoga.com, You will have opportunities to post messages or other information in public forums. Please understand that when You post such information, it is made public and is not subject to this policy. We are not responsible for any third party's use of information You publicly disclose through Our Service.

From time to time, We may partner with companies whose products We believe will interest Our members. In conjunction with these partners, We may send promotional announcements and/or serve web-based advertisements on their behalf, as permitted by law. 

You may connect one or more social networks with Your yoga.com account. If You choose to do so, We will collect information from Your social networking account(s) and Your use of Our social features. 

## Disclosure of Information

We may share Your information within the Snapside family of companies. The Snapside family of companies that access Your information will follow practices that are consistent with the practices described in this Privacy Policy. In addition We may use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services on Our behalf. We do not authorize these companies to use or disclose Your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services We request of them.

We may offer joint promotions or programs that, in order for participation, will require information be shared with third parties. By participating in such joint promotions or programs, You consent to Our sharing of Your information. Please note that We do not control the privacy practices of these third party businesses.

We may disclose Yourpersonal information:

  1. to provide information and/or services to You;
  2. if required to do so by law or by regulatory authority;
  3. to provide statistical analysis and research;
  4. marketing, market research and customer profiling;
  5. data analysis;
  6. if We believe in good faith that such action is necessary:
  7. to comply with any law or comply with legal process served on Us; 
    1. to protect and defend Our rights or property;
    2. to any regulatory body or licensing body or authority;
    3. to third parties for the purposes of settling or making payment in connection with any wager;
    4. to any payment management or debt collection company engaged by Us to handle payment and collection processes to and from Users;
    5. to third parties who provide services to Us or on our behalf;
    6. to any third party that purchases Us or Our business or any part of Us or Our business if it is allowed according to the applicable law;
  8. with Your consent; or
  9. for the purposes of disaster recovery.

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in this Privacy Policy, We may disclose Your personal information to Our employees, employees of Our affiliate group companies. All recipients of Your personal information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws and provisions of this Privacy Policy to keep Your information private. 

## Social Sharing

You may elect to share information about Youruse of the yoga.com service, within yoga.com as well as on other social networks. 

Other Websites and Platforms

The yoga.com Service may be provided through platforms or contain links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of information may differ from Ours. While We endeavor to associate with reputable companies, Snapside cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other websites and platforms. These websites and platforms have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which We recommend You to read carefully. In addition, You may encounter third party applications that interact with the yoga.com. To learn more about these, see our Terms of Use.

## Children

You must be 14 years of age or older to subscribe to the Yoga.com service. 

## Right to Access Your Information

We give You access to a broad range of information about Your account and Your interactions with Us in the "Your Account" portion of the website yoga.com. You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the personal information You provide to Us relating to Your account. You must be signed in to access "Your Account."If You have a question regarding Our privacy practices, or want to exercise Your rights regarding Your personal information, please contact Us at [support@yoga.com](mailto:support@yoga.com).

## Cookies and Other Technologies to Enhance Our Service

As You interact with Our service, We and Our service providers may place cookies on Your system. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to Your browser from a web server and stored on Your system for record keeping purposes. In general, cookies can make the Internet more useful by storing information about Your preferences on a particular system.

## Ads Displayed on Third Party Sites

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information about Your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to You. 

## Other Sources

We may collect or receive information from other sources including (i) cookies and other automatically collected information (ii) other Snapside users who choose to upload their email contacts; and (iii) third party information providers. This information will be used to supplement Your profile - primarily to help You and your friends connect. It will be combined with other information We collect.

## Security

Snapside takes information security very seriously and uses reasonable administrative, technical, physical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. 

Unfortunately, We cannot guarantee the absolute security of Your information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using Our service, including Our website and user interfaces, or providing information to Us through any means, You agree that we can communicate with You electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to Your use of the yoga.com Service.

## Changes to This Policy

As We update and expand Our Services, We may make changes to this policy. Although We shall endeavor to post a notification regarding such changes, You should check back for updates to this policy from time to time. You acknowledge that Your assent to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy subsequent to any changes made following Your initial consent as well as Your use of the yoga.com website or continued use of Our service after Our posting of changes to this policy, means that You agree to be bound by such changes. The most current version of this Privacy Policy can be reviewed by visiting Our website and clicking on "Privacy Policy". The most current version of the Privacy Policy will supersede all previous versions.

## Your Privacy Rights 

We do not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless You affirmatively agree to such disclosure, typically by "opting in" to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our sites. If You do ask Us to share your personal information with a third party for its marketing purposes, We will only share information in connection with that specific promotion, as We do not share information with any third party (other than our service providers) on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of Your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when You provide personal information on one of Our sites.

You can write to Us at any time to review, change, obtain a copy of Your information or have Your details altered or corrected in accordance with Your rights under the provisions of applicable law. 

## Consent to Privacy Statement

By using the Service, You agree to this Privacy Policy. This is Our entire and exclusive Privacy Statement and it supersedes any earlier version. Your continued use of the Service constitutes Your agreement to this Privacy Policy, as may be amended from time to time.

## Contacting Us

If You have questions concerning Your account, please contact Us. If You have questions concerning this Privacy Policy, including the treatment of Your personal information and/or our use of cookies and other technologies, please contact Us via email at [support@yoga.com](mailto:support@yoga.com)
